Guide to the Susan G. Bell papers SC1287
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Susan G. Bell papers
1652-2015 (inclusive), 1930s-2015 (bulk)
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Bell, Susan G.
SC1287
31.5 Linear Feet (21 cartons)
Biographical / Historical
Susan Groag Bell was a Senior Scholar at the Clayman Institute for Gender Research at Stanford University. Born in Troppau, Czechoslovakia, in 1926, she moved to the United States via England after World War II. Bell earned an AB at Stanford in 1964, and an MA from the University of Santa Clara in 1970. Bell was a pioneer in the field of Women’s History and feminist studies. She died June 24, 2015.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift, 2016.
Scope and Contents
Collection primarily consists of research files on women's history, correspondence, and photographs.
Feminist Studies; Women’s history; Bell, Susan G.; Clayman Institute for Gender Research
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2016-109
  - Meridea Court, 1984 May (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Copies of Sue's baby pictures with parents, 1973 Jul (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Avi Loures WAWH (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Garden, lounge, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Prints from slides (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Wedding, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - England Cumberland, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Afra's photographs, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1987 Jun (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Sue: England, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Sue: England, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Clare plants, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Family portraits, 1970 May (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Robert Clare, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - England, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - France, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Paul Elizabeth on beach, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Ron, Boston, N. Hampshire, NY, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - England, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - France England, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - England, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Bookowner lecture, 1977 Feb (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - England, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - England Anne Ridler Laura, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - New Year's Eve, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - with the kays at Fly in, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - England, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Shipton construction, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Oxford, 1984 May (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Helen's pictures house exterior, 1984 Jul (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - 1984 Nov (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Summer house pictures, 1985 Apr (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Bill Judith Kotys photographs of Shipton, 1984 Oct (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - SB at Hartfield house Aug Charleston, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Laura Doves pregnant Miscellaneous photographs, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - France, 1995 Summer (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Sussex Chichester Glasbow Paris Berlin lePuy, 1996 Summer (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - 1996 Summer (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - le Puy Polignae orange, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Farewell to Iris Dukes, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Iris Victor, 1997 Summer (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - 101 Alma St - 503 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 101 Alma - 503 Peter's 70th birthday, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 101 Alma Wendy Klaine new bedding (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Oxford, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Forest avenue, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Laura's graduation DC, circa 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Clare Matt Michael IRWG, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Mollie's birthday 20th IRWG, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Paris Elaine Block's Apt Angers Sussex, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Shipton Mary S-W Ruth Shepherd Kay E Keva, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Summer France, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Summer France, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Louise Woodside Sculpture Park, Vic's 80th birthday, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Summer, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Oppenshaw Golden wedding, circa 1996 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Betsy's birthday, 1995, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Hat parties, 1996-1999 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Cherries (Louisa's garden), 1991 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Munich, Vienna, Klara at Brownsea, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Oslo Clare Sussex Afra Scotland, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Hat party, 2001, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Napa Valley Yountville British graduate students in 101, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - London Edinburgh Botanics, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - London, Edinburgh Dijon, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - PACOA xmas party, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Abernant (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Clare and Sue and Ron in Woodside (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Family photographs (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Hanka, GBS house (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Hedy Tony Fromings (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous family (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous friend photographs (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Oxford (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Seattle (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Sue's publicity pictures, 1975 Nov (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Thanksgiving (Wendy) (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - 14 France (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 9-13 German (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 15 (portraits) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 14th German (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Witches (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 15th Century Italy (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 18th England (2) (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Early 20th Century Estelle Freedman's Student photographs (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 19th Century America (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - England slides, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 19 US Educ/work/dress (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Susan Bell complete set 100 spare slides used by Joan Moon, 1974 Summer (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - 19th E portraits (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - 19th Century Europe continental (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - 19 England II (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - 20th Century non-US or Europe (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Italy, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Lady Warisick lecture (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - 16th Century Ren. Germany (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - 17th Century Europe Italian, Dutch, German (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - 17th England (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - 2 Arfin (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Flemish Dutch 15th Century (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - 15th German (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - 14th Century Italy (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - 8-14 England (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - 14-15 Bohemia (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - 5-13 France (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Nuns (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - 15th Century England (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Mid - Europe - House (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Slavery and black women (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Renaissance England 16th Century (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Spare Americans (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - 16 Italy (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - 20 France (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - 16th Century Fleush Dutch (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Leanor FINI (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Levis factory (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Shipton CT (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - 17th Century France reason (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - French revolution approx. (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Book Owners (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - FILOLI garden (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - 20th US (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Oriental Women Ch J (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Modern/Hist Jewish (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - 18th Century France (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - 18th Century England (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Suffrage (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Colonial America (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Judy Chicago dinner party (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - 20th Century German (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - 19th Century Victorian England (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - England, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - 18 German/Dutch/Swiss Russ. Italian (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - 20th England (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Slides from Sorter Institute Workshop (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - 20th Europe (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Peppy from France (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - 20 Century Science (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - 19 France (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Rousham House, Oxfordshire (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Musee Carnavalet France (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Belles Heures Duke de Berry (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - 15th France II (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Bosch active 1480-1516 c. 1453-1516 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Hildegard of Bingen (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Eastern Women Persia, India (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - 16 French (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - 5-13 Spain, Italy (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - 15 France I (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Cult of the Virgin Eve (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Mexican pre-conquest (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Byzantine (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Egypt, Sumer, Crete (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Fert. Figs, cave art Anatolia Neolithic Britain (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Hungary Other European- BC (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Greeks (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - 16 German (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Etruscan Rome- Emp. Early Xtian (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Aged 7 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Boy? Friends (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Shipton Court Summer house (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - St. Clair (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 1933 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - New Year's Eve party, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Friends, 1945-1948 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 1939-1948 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, weddings, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Living room, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Rose garden, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Garden, 1984 May (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - 1984 May (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Freddy - wedding (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Other people's children (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - England, circa 1981 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - 1982 Sep 19 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Shipton, CT for rent, 1983 Jun (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - 1984 May (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - 1984 Jun (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Summer house, 1984 Oct (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Summer house exterior, 1984 Oct (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Snow, 1985 Jan (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Summer, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - France Summer, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Charleston garden paintings #1, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Charleston garden paintings #2, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Abernant reunion, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Dor Dogne, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Dor Dogne Verbier, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Lausanne, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Salzburg University, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Summer, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Edinburgh, Salzburg, Countess Razumovsky, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Salzburg festival Peter, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - 12-1 enlargements (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 6 Brusgids Weaga from of Libe? (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Chateau de Chateaudun (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - "Between Worlds" insert (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Betweem Worlds (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 1st prints of Le Livere de Trois Vibus (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Kyoto (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Postcards (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Greetings (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Margo Davis (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Mrs. S. Groag Haywards Heath St (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Sue Lillian at Prince M., 1983 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - from Klara Bushnell (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Winter, 1984 Feb (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Shipton (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Shipton, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Dr. Grosy (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - 1940 Jul-1942 Jan (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Selpi negatives (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Penny's LA ranch (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - S. multi A. W., 1983 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - R's birthday at San Salido, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - H SF ready, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - before 1999 Sep 26 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Gisellschaft (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Susi (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Laudschuaft (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - For Mrs. Grovy (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Film -foto E. Schafranek (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Mrs. Grovy 14232-33 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Unemploy and, Susi would bring it back! (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - before 1999 Sep 14 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - before 1999 Sep 14 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - before 1999 Sep 14 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - before 1950 Feb (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - before 1977 Apr (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Grandfather Wolf (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - before 1988 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - before 1987 Jan (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - W, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - 185 Louise at 193 H. (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Heron - Woodside (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Sue Catherine office, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Peggy, Lawrence, Robinson, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Clare and her dragon (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - 1984 Oct (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Eva Al photographs (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Prague (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Lindfield Vicerage 16 Summer hill (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - M. 15 Merider (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Hammond (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Ancient photographs, baby weight, doctor certificate (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - copies of early Shipton pics. Poor (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Mutti photographs (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Upstairs bathroom, 1984 Jun (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - The Loft (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Exterior of house (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - 18 Merider Court London (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Shipton, Peter/Billy, 1985 Summer (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - prior to 1987 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - only copy of SGB aged 4/5/6/or 7 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - 101 Alma street - 503 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Baby, 1986 Nov (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Oxford Alums, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - St. Louis Obispo, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - 1986 Mar (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - 1985 Aug 25 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Wedding, 1986 Jun (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - 1983 Nov (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Visual Art SVC (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Fracture (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Gardeniums (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Oxford lecture sex (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Oxford suff. Lecture V (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - unnamed (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Lady Warwick spares (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Warwick paper (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Sevrdea lecture Dominican, 1993 Apr 17 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Tapestry lecture overflow (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - lecture 18 C Engl. Q gardens (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Oxford educ. Lecture III (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - to label (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Belles Heures Duke de Berry (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - bookowners (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Brassels slides originals from Xtine (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - England out of focus, 1981 Aug/Sep (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - IRWG- 20th anniversary (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Vanessa slides Caddes Sue Bell (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Xtine tapestry (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - 18M Euge gardens (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Xtine de Pizan special lecture (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Slides (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - study Xtine (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - pizan extras (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - unlabeled (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - slides for ASUL (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Vanessa's garden slides (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Oxford sex lecture 2 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - unnamed slides (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Vanessa garden slides (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - 19th century England duplicates (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Plastic slide mount (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Journals (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Publicity and News Clippings (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Teaching Notes (Index Cards) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence personal (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Jan Groag (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Personal correspondence (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Personal correspondence (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Xtine Garden (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Tapestry correspondence (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Marg - Austria (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Xtine correspondence (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Bookownership article (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Margaret at Austria (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Christine lecture (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Stansky (Hist Today) (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Letters to Charlotte (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Mayhall/ History (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Birth certificate, Father's death certificate (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Mother 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Autogtaph letters, Sue diplomas (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Sue's Stanford study (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Stories (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Wachtel (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Eitner (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - unnamed (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - SB personal (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Stories- correspondence (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Lillian Frust Lillian Groag (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - unnamed (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Freddy (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Clare documents (old current) Clare (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - NEH Stipend prop '96 yal fund-00 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - SB lectures, 1980- (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - S - students (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Recommendations (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Groag font (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Laura Mayhall (PhD) (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Rosalind/ Devana Pavilk (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Assembly programs (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Contributors' agreements (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Weaver the Hammonds (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - unlabeled (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Susan Ann, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 2007 Jan 14 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - unlabeled (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - unlabeled (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - unlabeled (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 1998 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - 1996 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - 1999 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 1997 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - unlabeled (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - with Duncan Robinson, 1999 Sep 2 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Hat party, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - at Mt. Hood, 2003 Jun (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - unlabeled (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - 1999 Sep (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Ashdown house, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - in Kensington, 1999 Aug 31 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Pep Harris Nathen Christmas, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Itinerary (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - 2006 Oct 12 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - 1994 Feb 9 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - From Mr. and Mrs. Offen, 1974 Jun 4 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Paris, 1997 Sep 2 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Susan Groag bottom row, 2nd from left, 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - 2006 Jul (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Charleston farmhouse (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - 1999 Sep (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Postcards (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - 1967 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Pacoa party, 2004 Dec 18 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Betsy's birthday, 1996 Sep (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Summer, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Lelezna Ruda (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Thank you card, 1999 Sep 25 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - 1999 Sep 26 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Vill, biebe (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Christmas card, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Llanwrtyd Wells (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Hearst Castle postcard (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - 1958 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Peare Draheim, 1999 Sep 23 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Lihaschowitz, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Photographs (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - V A tapestries (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Opava photographs, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Opava photographs, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Opava photographs, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Opava photographs, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Opava photographs, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Provence Switz Lilly Hilde, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Passhurst E. Houses (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Cartridge hatfield (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Prague - Mara (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Opava Modern flats, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Olomone, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Opava, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - 185 Forest/3A, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Atra - Bridget other friends (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Slavonice (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Zamek Telc (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Zamek Telc (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Telc (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Telc, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Susan Groag (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Lillian Groag Pasadena, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Telc prague festival (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - 101 Alma ov 2, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Slavonice Prague Skana, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Melc, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - 1954 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 1955 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - 1956 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 1956 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - 1968 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - 1969 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 1970 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 1971 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - 1972 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - 1973 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - 1974 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - 1975 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - 1976 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - 1977 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - 1978 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - 1978 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - 1979 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - 1980 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - 1981 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - 1982 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - 1985 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - 1986 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - 1987 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - 1990 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - 1992 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - 1993 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - 1994 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - 1995 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - 1996 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - 1997 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - 1998 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - 1999 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - 2000 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - 2001 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Helps to Worship (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Letters (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Mrs. S. Barrington HP 8 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - unlabeled (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - unlabeled (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - 1959 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - 1974 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - 1983 Sep-1984 Dec (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - 1988 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - 1989 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - 1991 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - 2001 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 2002 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - 2003 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - 2004 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 2005 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 2006 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - 2007 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - 2008 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - 2009 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - 2010 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - 2011 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - 2012 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - 2013 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - 2014 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - 2015 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - unlabeled (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Susan Bell w. Alan Feuley KALW, 1991 Jan 3 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Messages, 1999 Apr (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - John Knox recorded and broadcast, 2000 Sep/Oct (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Rosenthal, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - SGB cont. studies Autobiography discuss, 1992 Feb 6 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Sue Bell KALW (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - IRWG discuss tapestry book project, 1995 Nov 6 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - KALW- SGB, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Menschenbilder Radio Austria 1, 2012 Dec 8 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Menschenbilde: Susan Groag Bell, 2012 Dec 8 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Tapestry seminar IRWG, 1993 Oct 13 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - New Year messages, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Interview on BBC SCR (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Menschenbilder Radio Austria 1, 37598 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Menscenbilder Radio Austria 1, 2012 Dec 8 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Sir Peter Shepherd, Oliviar Ben, Afra Olviar Ben, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Oulyou kit ride only, Jan 4 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - unlabeled (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Lilian Furst Adams Lectures, 2009 Sep 29 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Photograph albums, publicity posters (Box 15, Folder 0)
  - Personal correspondence, 2000-2006 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Personal correspondence, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence to keep (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Ron (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - 1967 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - 1967 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - 1965 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - 1965 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - 1977 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - 1978 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - 1979 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - 1980 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - 1981 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - 1982 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - 1926 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - 1939 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - 1947 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - 1952 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - 1955 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - 1956 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - 1957 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Old Letters Groag, 1920s (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - de la part de W. Dulac (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Answered letters received in Oxford (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Bookmark (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Sue multi, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Santa Barbara PCB, circa 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Negatives (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Negatives (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Shipton negatives (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Brok Perk Stanford press, 1983 Nov 1 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - 1983 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Negatives (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Shipton/Craden multi in Winkergarden, 1983 Summer (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Shipton interiors in Servite house, 1983 May (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Shipton suttering (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Shipton Ct. Summerhouse 1st time, 1982 Sep 19 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - W. / Farmer Brown (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - House (Shipton) (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Shipton/Oxford winter, 1983 Feb (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Negatives (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Negatives (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Negatives (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Shipton Palo Alto interior of furnished house, 1984 Oct (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Negatives, 1990s (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Santa Clara, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Negatives (Box 18, Folder 23)